let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:
            "Huruf Apa Ini? あ",
        answer: "A",
        options: [
            "E",
            "Ne",
            "A",
            "Fu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Huruf Apa Ini? し",
        answer: "Shi",
        options: [
            "Shi",
            "Ne",
            "Fu",
            "Ta"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Huruf Apa Ini? れ",
        answer: "Re",
        options: [
            "Nu",
            "E",
            "Ke",
            "Re"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Huruf Apa Ini? ね",
        answer: "Ne",
        options: ["Ne", "I", "Wo", "Fu"] 
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Huruf Apa Ini? ち",
        answer: "Chi",
        options: ["Wo", "Nn", "Chi", "Ra"]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Huruf Apa Ini? ふ",
        answer: "Fu",
        options: ["Fu", "Ta", "Ne", "No"]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Huruf Apa Ini? め",
        answer: "Me",
        options: ["Sa", "So", "Na", "Me"]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Huruf Apa Ini? ぬ",
        answer: "Nu",
        options: ["O", "E", "Ka", "Nu"]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Huruf Apa Ini? の",
        answer: "No",
        options: ["Ri", "Nn", "Tsu", "No"]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Huruf Apa Ini? え",
        answer: "E",
        options: ["Ta", "Ke", "E", "Nn"]
    }
];
